And I will show you every single click,
so nobody gets lost. After you
downloaded the skills, you have two zip
files. Just unzip them, double click,
and you get two normal folders. I will
also provide the normal folders, so
everyone can do this. One is the
Instagram engine skill, and the other
one is the dataset builder skill. Now,
we bring them to Clo open your file
window and go to your home folder.
That's the one with your username on it.
The folder we need is called dot Clo,
and it's hidden on Mac. Inside the dot
Clo, there's a folder called skills. If
it's not there, just create it. Right
click, new folder, and name it skills.
Now, drag both skills folders in there.